Brother, your bike has been stolen.
[screaming sound]
Meenakshi, you didn't get my bike stolen, did you?
Brother, I have eaten your salt.  How
can I do this?
Hey, then who stole it?
Brother, let's go to the police station and file a report there.
No, I can't trust the law.
I know a Baba.  He will
tell me who stole my bike.
Then let's go to Baba.  Yes, okay, come on
Baba, my bike has been stolen. Boy, first give me
Dakshina. Yes, take this Baba, now tell me
what colour was the bike. Baba, my bike was black in
colour. I will find out and tell you. The
age of your bike which has been stolen is between 10 to 5 years.
Baba, do one thing, take out his picture and give it to me.
Okay, I will take out the photo but it will
cost extra Rs 2000.  Baba, not just Rs 2000, you
can keep all the money but please take his photo and
give it to us once.  Hema Malini, the owner of the mistress,
took out the photo.  Here you go
[music] I've got a snake, not a brother, a
snake.  Today you sold the bike, tomorrow you will sell it to me.
[Laughter]